wondering his career averages against
the Sacramento Kings averages 27.5
points per game
[Music]
four dollars
yeah
I'm on my way right now
it's 3 10.
well I'm looking at a thousand dollars
of Italian engineering says everyone's
early
Johnson kiss my ass he had his chance
with the weather account his door closed
and my door opened well John's actually
here Pete so why don't you do this is my
moment Craig my future you understand me
if you let him in that room I swear to
God I will make sure
what if the Weller reps want to get
started stall Craig lie to them I'm
stuck in traffic
any towels man paper towels
house not you
what
what did I just say
anybody
screws this pitch up before I get in
there anybody
I will kill them do you understand me I
will literally shoot them in the house
all right
don't tell me to calm down
can I help you with something Mr Clean
not you [ __ ]
you are a bad person
and you're a janitor
one day you might just get a good look
at yourself
one day
he might not like what you see
whatever helps you work at night
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
it's occupied
hey I'm gonna be here a minute [ __ ]
[Music]
hey
hey what is happening out there
all right you want me to come out there
hey
what is going on out here
[Music]
foreign
hey
hey [ __ ] open up
[Music]
talk to time
okay I'm gonna be here a minute [ __ ]
[Music]
hey
ah what is happening out there
[Music]
what the hell is happening out there
what was happening out there
hey what the hell is happening out there
[Music]
thank you
all right you want me to come out there
[Music]
look up
hey I know this is weird but you're
trapped in it
time paradox
yeah it's time travel yeah I don't know
it's just happening forward backward
minutes or seconds totally random time
travel
one door opens another closes fix the
paradox
kill your future
what you were right
you were right
about the Stalls you just go in come out
that's how it works
oh
I just told
me that
this isn't real that's what I said
you're not real that's what I said
go into the song you'll see
I'm not going anywhere that's what I say
that's what I
I know you're freaked out
believe me
a couple minutes ago when I was you I
didn't believe me either
but if you go into that stall you come
back out you're going to be right where
I'm standing now
and you'll see what I'm talking about
I'll see
you will be me
no
what no no what
this is different
I didn't say that this is all different
okay time travel
so there's like a timeline
dead guy's watch is broken here at 3 30.
that's
10 minutes from now by my watch
it's 12 by mine okay so you are two
minutes from where I am and then there's
something about folding a piece of paper
and pushing them
pencil through it
we're doing 80s time travel I'm here
you're here we die here somehow we're
gonna make it out of here live we've got
to keep here from happening right
so we go here instead create a new
timeline
that's how Dr Marty did it
okay
easy
you're me from the future right yeah so
I just do something you did Future's
changed new timeline
no that's the problem
I went into the stall again and you
didn't you should already be me but
you're nuts that's the Paradox now we
both just exist
right
okay so the note said kill the future
close the door close so so
you're from the future
yeah
oh come on look I'm not saying it's
pretty but if you
and I
can do this and why would I do that
looks like you already have I don't even
have a gun sure you do where did that
thing even come from it came from you I
don't have it then take it from who
yourself why do I have because you took
it look it's time travel don't overthink
it
I got a meeting yet too what the meeting
whoa let's overthink this I want to
overthink this
look man you can't change the future
you're from the future
two minutes and that means that I'm in
the past so I should be the one to
change the future no because what if I'm
in the future from the past
if you're in the future how can you
change it it's got to be me in the past
changing the future
no no no okay fine you're right but look
Marty McFly McFly's dad you kissed your
mom now I go into the stall that's me
punching Biff you shoot yourself that
bullet's your DeLorean
you mean lightning strike yeah whatever
as long as it kills you
hey look at me the writing's on the
toilet paper okay
your door closes and my door opens kill
your future that's what it says
and that's you
I'll thank myself later
nice
it's very
that's very Charming
kill your future that's what it says and
that's you
I'll thank myself later
when it gets in the way
I'm going to take one for the team Pete
you look like a good guy to me
your door closes
my door
[Music]
come on
who are you
I'm me who are you
but I just
so we're right back where we started
what are you doing
I'm gonna try again well what do you
mean try again
well you came out before I did so your
future me
yeah so there's the gun kill the future
I just went through this with the other
no I just went through this with the
other guy okay so then you know whoa
hold up
that's not fair
yeah that's what the other guy said
foreign
[Music]
at first I didn't off himself that's
what happened I knew I couldn't trust
myself wait what's not working now we
just keep spawning morons
what did you just say he called you a
[ __ ] guys let's just chill
he's you idiot you're calling me who's
the idiot then Lauren it's working
[Music]
that's the problem
we just keep creating more paradoxes
every step is a step in the wrong
direction
[Music]
hey this is it
what last requests
what
I finally get it
you don't fix a paradox gentleman
[Music]
you finish it
time to close some doors
[Music]
[Applause]
let me out
get in that stall
what are you doing
right now what why are you doing this
why
because there's one body unaccounted for
and that's you in that stall at 3 30.
get in the store get in put your jacket
back on
[Music]
I can still make the end of it to the
meeting
you're crazy yeah you and me both okay
don't do this shut up
I've I've got just as much dude
who do you think you're talking to
I know all your little tactics oh you're
[ __ ] at the end of the day you're
just a manipulative [ __ ] aren't you
you want me to feel bad about this
for a fact that you do the same
your door closes and my door opens
I'll thank myself later
you really are a bad person
any last requests
maybe just a little privacy
[Music]
thank you
hey this is it
what last requests
no
[Music]
wait
foreign
[Music]
thank you